Hey, I...
Nice, just who I wanted to see.
What's up?
Oh, hey, how's it going, Rika?
Rika does not appreciate your crappy tone.
I don't think I've ever seen you without your glasses before.
Rika thought it'd be fun to do something different for a change.
Maybe Rika should dye her hair next.
You're wearing contacts now?
Actually, Rika doesn't need to wear glasses at all.
Huh?
That's right, Rika's vision is perfect.
If you don't have to wear them, then what's the point?
Rika is being fashionable, isn't it obvious?
Did the word fashionable seriously come out of your mouth?
How about character design?
Oh, yeah, that sounds more up your alley.
Despite what you think, Rika's more than some nerdy scientist stuck in a lab all day.
So, surely you now find Rika sexier than ever.
Huh?
Hmm.
Who knew such a sex fiend could come across as naive and innocent by simply taking off her glasses?
As for whether I'd hit that or not, I'd have to say,
hells yeah.
You could show some restraint.
Rika's sitting right here.
Wait a second.
I actually said that out loud?
Yeah, you dummy.
Ah!
What did you do that for?
Beats me.
Ugh, rotten hell.
How primal.
Uh, when did the rest of you get here?
Well, aren't you a dirty boy?
Rika never knew you harbored such a lustful desire for her supple body.
Force Rika onto this table and take her from behind!
Shut up!
Oh my, perhaps Rika should speak with more eloquence.
A touch of class is the way to a man's heart.
Would you please rip off Rika's clothes and give her your sweet manhood?
How is that a touch of class?
Man, of all people, you just had to be Rika.
Is desiring Rika so painful?
Observe the tears welling up in her eyes.
Well, I guess I'd better start hitting the book.
He dares to pour salt into the open wound of Rika's heart?
Though Rika must admit, as much as it hurts, it also feels good.
Rika is dripping wet!
Have it your way.
Rika will once again retreat from her cruel reality and escape to a better world.
Hey Senna, may Rika please use the TV?
Oh yeah, sure.
What game are you going to play?
It's not a game.
Rika's going to watch Homo Game Club.
It arrived in the mail just yester...
Seriously, what makes you think we'd let you watch that garbage in here?
Homo Game Club isn't garbage!
The title may be kind of weird,
and the game it's based on is only for players who are 18 and up.
But all the naughtier parts have been watered down for the movie.
They wanted to make sure kids could watch it too.
Heck, even your grandma would like it.
All the steamy love scenes have been replaced with more subtle hotness.
So now it's not as explicit and appeals to a broader audience.
Big deal.
Who wants to watch two dudes snuggle up?
Rika loves watching men get busy.
How could you not stare at this cover for hours?
Get that thing out of my face right now.
See, I told you, it's not a porno.
Fine, it's not porn,
but any movie with that creepy a title
and three naked dudes side-by-side on the cover
is bound to be messed up.
Rika doesn't think you should simply judge a book by its cover
without taking a look at what's inside.
She's right.
People always jump to conclusions about stuff they know nothing about.
Rika knew you'd agree.
Try to get to know something
before you start throwing around assumptions.
It sucks to be judged just by how you look.
It sucks hardcore.
Um, yeah, go ahead and stick in the movie.
Way to get Yozara to change her mind.
As for you, get ready to feast your eyes on PG-rated man love.
This basically rehashes the TV show
with a few minor tweaks here and there.
You should be able to follow along without a problem.
Want to play with me?
What?
No, you'll never catch me playing that kinky stuff.
A fan-made game, huh?
I'm all ears, bro.
Are we going to do this together?
You can count on me.
Damn it!
Not a one!
We sold zero copies!
Damn it all to hell!
Shut up!
We're in this for more than sales!
We're in it for ourselves!
Homo Game Club, you're finished!
Finished forever!
You'll have to get past my rock-hard six-pack!
You're blocking the TV.
No matter the cost,
even if the entire world's against the two of us,
I'll never stop protecting you, Fumio.
Dummy, you know that's my line.
I'll be right by your side,
now and forever.
It's pretty touching stuff, wouldn't you say?
Uh, sure, I suppose it is.
It takes a lot of courage to open up like that,
but your secret's safe with me.
I promise.
Thank you.
Ah!
The best two hours of Rika's young life.
I'm just so happy I finally got to see it.
Rika?
Yeah?
Why did Fumio and Koyomi,
uh, you know,
why'd they kiss at the end?
Wait, for reals, yo?
When emotions are running high
in the heat of the moment,
people always kiss.
What?
But still,
those two guys were best friends,
and I thought,
friends couldn't kiss.
Of course they can!
Human impulse knows no boundaries.
Well, even so,
isn't that a little weird?
Kissing one of your friends just,
it seems wrong.
What are you talking about?
When two people feel the magic of romantical chemistry,
the next steps to kiss lips,
spread legs,
and scream to the neighbors come!
It don't matter if they're best friends,
it don't matter if they're two dudes!
What matters is they best be getting busy under the sheets!
Two naked men going at it!
Rika thanks God for this precious gift!
Maybe you should stick to your dirty robot comics from now on.
I see.
Even friends kiss each other when the time is right.
I will admit,
I should never have judged Homo Game Club that way.
Awesomeness!
Does this mean you'll join Rika
as a member of the Homo Game Club fan club?
Uh, I'll have to get back to you on that one.
Right now,
I'll just say it was better than I expected.
That's all.
Rika's ecstatic that you enjoyed it so much!
And if you've got any other good stuff,
feel free to bring it up to the club.
On it!
Finally, Rika's got her first friend!
But this friendship might not last
if Rika can't produce another movie.
Think hard, Rika.
What's another fun one?
My Baby Maker can't be this cute
as another homoerotic masterpiece,
but it's out of print!
And Squid or Octopus Don't Make Me Choose
goes right for the tentacle wreath!
This is so unfair!
What's wrong now, me?
Don't act like you don't know!
You're always slamming my dating games
and calling them creepy as hell!
What makes Rika's gay shows any better?
Hm.
Homo Game Club is about the importance of true friendship,
a theme that's relevant to this club.
Don't compare it to the ridiculous filth
that's on your computer 24-7.
There's no comparison.
Hey, you haven't even played one yet,
so how would you know?
If your dumb games are so appropriate,
then try reading one of the scenes out loud for us.
Hm.
Why don't you do the one you're on right now?
Judging by your expression,
you can't wait to share it.
Um, this particular scene
isn't the most accurate representation of the game.
That doesn't matter.
I could read any scene
out of Homo Game Club out loud
and it'd still seem normal.
There's a lot more to it
than just getting reamed in the forest.
All right, then.
Go ahead and try it.
Oh, I remember this part.
I'm ready.
Hit play.
No matter the cost,
even if the entire world's against the two of us,
I'll never stop protecting you, Fumio.
You dummy, you know that's my line.
There's nothing that we can't conquer
as long as we have each other.
That was the ending.
Of course it sounds cool and dramatic.
Let's try out a different scene.
This one.
Ain't no one gonna break my stride
and ain't no one gonna slow me down.
I've got to keep on moving
no matter what stands in my way.
Ah!
Really?
There's got to be crappy sounding lines
somewhere in this movie.
Oh, they took all the best scenes
from the TV show, remember?
Don't ever be ashamed
of who you really are inside.
Everyone will have their doubters,
but you can't let anyone else decide
who you are.
No!
Not another cool one!
Who knew guys could be such smooth talkers?
Don't underestimate me, Sal.
How did she already memorize the entire movie?
Now then, I think I've proven my point well enough.
Your turn.
Ah!
Let me hear a scene
from one of your dating games.
What's wrong, sandbags?
If there's nothing to be ashamed of,
then you've got nothing to be afraid of.
The dialogue in this scene should do nicely
whenever you're ready.
Go on.
Do it.
Now!
Fine, no big deal.
It's just like the movie.
It's not like there's going to be
anything remotely dirty.
Besides, a girl ought to be able to say
whatever she likes
without having catty people judge her.
By the time I'm through,
I'll prove to you that one day
I suddenly got a blonde little sister
with pigtails and I can't take it anymore
is a work of art.
Maybe even a masterpiece!
Is that really the title?
Okay, here we go.
My brother,
give me your big, juicy...
thick...
What?
Big brother,
give me your big, juicy...
juicy...
your, um...
thick...
Louder, clearer, and more feeling.
How about using some emotion?
Big brother,
I want you to give me
your big, juicy, thick...
and drench me with your hot,
sticky...
until I'm gasping for air there.
I fucking said it!
The End
Wow, she really did it.
Did you think you were going to win
every single battle against me?
Gotta hand it to you, Meat.
I never thought you'd say that.
Yeah?
Too bad.
Don't underestimate me.
More importantly,
I've proved that my dating games
aren't embarrassing at all.
Oh, okay.
I guess you've kind of beat me this time.
At least look at my face
when you admit it.
Rika's jealous
that even her supercharged libido
can't match up with yours.
That was impressive, Senna.
I had no clue
you were oozing
with so much sexual energy.
Yeah, no kidding.
Who would have thought?
I certainly have
a better understanding
of why your gaming habits
are what they are.
So I'm sorry
for making fun of you.
You're all a bunch
of dumb perverts.
Screw you!
Well, here's to finally
being done with finals.
Hey, you there
with the freaky hairdo.
Come on, turn around,
my little lamb.
Don't leave a sister hanging.
Turning your back
on a servant of God like me
is basically buying yourself
a one-way ticket to hell.
I'm sorry,
but are you by any chance
talking to me?
Well, naturally.
Who else has got hair
like that?
Oopsie-daisy.
Who says oopsie-daisy?
What do you want from me?
Just figured I'd let you know
that if you need anyone
to talk to, I'm open ears.
It's a sister's duty.
Well, I guess I do have
my share of problems.
I can tell.
Life's been gumming
at you fast, am I right?
Some people will even mess
with their appearance
to deal with the stress.
Sorry, but if you're
referring to my hair,
that's actually
its natural color.
What?
That's natural?
Oh, who would have
thunk it?
Yep, no one ever said
hard living was easy.
What does that mean?
I gotta run,
but it was nice meeting you.
Yeah, if you have any issues,
just swing by the counseling center
and hit me up.
The name's Kate Takayama, okay?
Some kids call me Mother Kate,
since a lot of them
are younger than me.
Takayama?
Big Brother!
I finally found you!
You can't get away from me!
Hey, that girl over there.
Do you know her?
Get away from Big Brother right now,
you poopy old hag!
I guess I'll take that
as a yes.
Maria!
Keep it up, kiddo!
I dare ya!
Ow!
Quit, stupid face!
I'll kill ya!
What?
Don't you remember
what you're supposed to call me?
You dummy!
Fart freckles, idiot!
Fart freckles!
Now there's an impressive vocabulary.
Die!
Die, poopy butt!
Pooper trooper!
Hurry up and say it, kid!
I love you, Big Sis!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, it hurts!
Stop it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please let go, forgive me!
I love you, Big Sister Poop!
Keep in coming, you brat!
I'm sorry, Big Sis,
for real this time!
So you must be Kodika Hasegawa,
am I right?
Oh, yeah.
That's cool.
My little sis talks about you a lot,
like non-stop.
Little sister?
Yep, I'm Maria's older sister.
Nice to meet ya.
Man, it does feel kind of weird,
seeing her big brother Kodika
for the first time and everything.
Maria's an idiot,
in case you haven't noticed.
So please look after her for me, okay?
You're the idiot!
Big brother hangs out with me
because he likes me,
not because your stupid face
tells him to!
Head!
Hey, you better get all your chores done!
Don't want a poopy head!
Ugh, what a pain.
Seriously,
how can someone so idiotic
be related to me?
It sucks.
But I am grateful for your help.
Yours and everyone else
is in that group you hang out with.
And which group is that?
You call it the neighbor's club, right?
Maria's been in a better mood
ever since she became
the club's advisor.
Oh, is that right?
I figured she had always
been pretty optimistic.
Actually, the opposite.
Long story short,
she feels a lot more comfortable
in the classroom
than outside of it.
She's real cocky
about her grades,
so she has trouble
making friends,
and it's gotten worse
since she started skipping ahead.
So it's good she has you
to hang out with
when she's lonely.
Your little sister as well,
the chick vampire.
Oh, and also
Yozora Mikazuki.
I basically owe that girl
a thank you card.
Wait, for Yozora?
We were way too easy on Maria
when she was younger,
and we kind of ended up
spoiling her.
But Yozora is willing
to deal with her attitude
and not let her have her way
every single time.
She treats Maria like a kid
instead of a prodigy or genius.
That's probably a lot better for her.
Having someone she can't
just look down on
to get what she wants
takes her out of her comfort zone.
Can't say I saw that one coming.
Props, Yozora.
Could you do a big favor for me, though,
and get Maria to quit flashing people
in broad daylight?
Uh, of course.
I'll talk to her about that.
Good.
Other than that,
thanks again for looking after her.
Thank you, big brother.
Right.
Did you say big brother?
You're Maria's big brother, aren't you?
So by default,
you're like my big brother, too.
I mean, I'm 15, so you're older.
Well, see you, bro.
Whew.
That's a wet one.
Kodaka.
I kind of figured
you'd be at the club room by now.
Nah.
Someone held me up for a while.
Somebody I know?
Hmm?
By the way, Kodaka.
Yeah?
Did you finish
all your final exams, too?
Yep.
I read about this thing
friends supposedly do after tests.
They get together
and compare answers
and see who got what
for which questions.
Uh, yeah,
I guess that's a friendly-sounding
sort of thing to do afterwards.
Yeah, it's pretty stupid.
I mean, it's not like
your grade's gonna get any better.
But that being said,
when we've got friends
of our own to talk to,
I'm sure we'll be forced
into doing the whole
compare answers thing
whether we like it or not.
Sure, it's possible.
So, yeah, I think...
Well, I think we should
probably start practicing
for the future.
You do see what
I'm getting at, right?
Yeah, okay.
Let's start.
Okay.
What was your answer
for the fourth question
of the third section
on the Math 2 exam?
For the math test?
But we took that one
on the first day.
How am I supposed
to remember the answers
when I can't remember
the question?
This is exactly what
I was afraid would happen
our first time.
What kind of question was it?
It was one of those math proofs
worth a decent chunk of credit.
Oh, that one, yeah.
My answer ended up
being really long.
I don't feel great about it.
Wait.
How are we supposed
to share answers
when we don't have
the tests in front of us
to compare?
Yeah, I guess that is
a pretty good point.
I think we're better off
just saying that one
was tough, or I'm pretty
sure I got it before we
actually try to answer
and do complicated things.
We are still just practicing.
Okay.
Hey, buddy, that question
was a toughie, don't you think?
Yeah.
Yeah, it sure was.
All right, we've got to do
it with a different
type of question.
Definitely.
Maybe like a multiple choice
or fill in the blank one.
Better yet, something
from today's exam.
Hmm, there was one today
that had me stumped.
The 11th blank in section
two of the history exam.
Give me a second.
Let me see.
After Hojo Tokimune's death,
vassal Adichiyasumori
was overthrown
by inner administrator
blank number 11.
It's obviously Taira Yoritsuna,
so I put him down.
Yeah, I doubt too many people
got that question wrong.
However, I think I may have
misspelled the name Yoritsuna
like with one letter off.
I better not get docked
a lot of points for that.
She wouldn't grade us
that harshly.
Yoritsuna or Yoritsuno.
One letter spells the difference
between passing and
blunking out of school.
That's the most
random mistake ever.
Then again.
You could have misspelled it too,
or maybe you botched
the whole thing
and you're screwed
for the rest of your life.
Now you've got me worried
about it.
I hope you're happy.
No, I must have put
Yoritsuna, didn't I?
We'll find out soon enough.
I felt pretty good about myself
till you opened
your damn mouth.
Comparing answers
is freaking stressful.
You got that one right.
Okay, then.
Why don't we move on
to the next one?
Number 18 in section two.
Okay.
In year one
of the Shochu era,
blank number 18.
Yeah, I took a random guess
on this one.
Year 1324.
Hmm?
Oh, hey,
how's it going, Senna?
What are you two doing?
Comparing answers?
Uh-huh.
That's awesome,
but I'll grace you both
with my knowledge.
You guys are lucky.
It's not often
that I tutor
the less fortunate.
What can I say?
I'm generous.
Beat it, Breasticles.
We don't need you.
Huh.
Bitch, what's your problem?
I've got all the answers
down pat.
Math 2, section 3,
question 5.
Answer now.
That one was
the square root of 5.
How are they memorizing
all the questions
by number?
Japanese, section 2,
question 1, part 3.
The Irregular Conjugation.
What?
Man, I said
it was the infinitive.
Better luck next time,
Yozera.
Come on, come on.
Ask me another one.
Buzz off.
Comparing answers
is a stupid waste
of time anyway.
It's not like it's going
to bump your grade up
or anything.
Here we go.
Hold on a sec.
Wait.
Just give me
one more question.
I don't care how hard it is.
It can be anything you want.
No.
Comparing answers with meat
is dumb and serves no purpose.
But don't tell me that.
Tell Mama,
who sat next to me
in 8th grade
told me the same thing.
Please.
I'd rather compare answers
with Tomo than with you.
Speaking of,
hey Tomo,
what did you put down
for question 7
on the bio exam?
Jerk!
Quit mumbling crazy
talk to yourself
when I'm right.
Oh, the answer to that
was Calvin Benson cycle.
I wasn't sure,
but I put Calvin Benson cycle.
Really?
You put that down too?
Then I bet
we got it right.
You're so awesome, Tomo.
Quit ignoring me,
douchebag!
Phew, we're finally through with final exams.
I hit the books harder than usual this year,
but they were still pretty rough.
Our school had finals after summer vacation
because it's on the two-term system.
The more you know, am I right?
Are you talking to Tomo again?
Anyway, we're not gonna have any more tests for a while.
Yeah, now there's plenty of time to study
for the next batch of tests.
Don't be a downer.
Next time on Hog and I Next,
my little sisters are this cute.
Kodaka, you really have a thing for your little sis?
Here we go.